(Raj:)I'm actually glad Lucy had to work tonight.
(Raj:)Saved me the awkward conversation about
how I was gonna be hanging with my bros.
(Howard:)Isn't every conversation you two
have awkward? Heh.
(Raj:)Painfully so. We have this rule on the phone
that if no one talks for three minutes...
(Raj:)...you can just hang up.
I'm so into her.
- Ready whenever you guys are.
- Yeah, we'll be right there.
(Sheldon:)- Leonard.
- Yeah?
(Sheldon:)I'm not sure how I feel about Howard
being Dungeon Master instead of you.
Aw. That's nice, but relax,
sometimes change is good.
(Leonard:)You were worried about Zachary Quinto
being the new Spock...
(Leonard:)...but you wound up liking him.
(Sheldon:)Please. Every time the topic of change comes
up you throw Zachary Quinto in my face.
(Sheldon:)I'm upset the mailman has a new haircut,
"Zachary Quinto."
(Sheldon:)I'm upset that daylight saving time started,
(Sheldon:)Daylight saving time ended,
"Zachary Quinto."
(Sheldon:)For the last time, Zachary Quinto
was a weird, wonderful, unrepeatable event.